{
    "subject": "resource/Hod_Stuart",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Ontario",
    "human_readable": "Hod Stuart was born in Ontario.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9020313024520874,
            "question": "Where was Hod Stuart born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8841254711151123,
            "question": "In what province or state was Hod Stuart born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8131324052810669,
            "question": "When was Hod Stuart born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.769554078578949,
            "question": "Has Hod Stuart lived in other places besides Ontario?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43937456607818604,
            "question": "What is Hod Stuart known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34183791279792786,
            "question": "Is there any information about Hod Stuart's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30143898725509644,
            "question": "What is Hod Stuart's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22925031185150146,
            "question": "Does Hod Stuart have any notable accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22492985427379608,
            "question": "Is there any information about Hod Stuart's education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2174137830734253,
            "question": "What is Ontario known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hod Stuart was born in Ontario.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6585_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about Hod Stuart's education?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6585_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Hod Stuart have any notable accomplishments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6585_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Hod Stuart's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6585_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6585_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6585_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6585_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6585_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6585_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6585_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6585_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6585_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6585_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6585_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe document with file_path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6585/re-ranker-msmarco/14.txt` and another with file_path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6585/re-ranker-msmarco/20.txt` mention that William Hodgson \"Hod\" Stuart was born in Ottawa, Ontario. This information supports the triple statement that Hod Stuart was born in Ontario."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that William Hodgson \"Hod\" Stuart was born on February 20, 1879, in Ottawa, Ontario, Canada. Therefore, the statement that Hod Stuart was born in Ontario is correct according to the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}